Shepherd: The Story of a Jewish Dog is a family,
drama, war film directed by Lynn Roth.
Follow the perilous journey to freedom when a young boy and his dog
attempt to escape a concentration camp during World War II.
Based on true events.
Joshua, played by August Maturo.
Shoshonna, played by Ayelet Zurer.
Ralph, played by Ken Duken.
Greta, played by Lois Robbins.
Mrs. Komorsky's Daughter, played by Rebeka Rea.
Stengel, played by Levente Molnár.
August Maturo (born August 28, 2007) is an American actor.
He is  best-known for his performance as Auggie Matthews on the Disney Channel sitcom Girl Meets World
and his recurring role as the voice of Puck McSnorter in Mickey and the Roadster Racers.
His notable film credits include the horror-thriller
films The Nun (2018) and Slapface (2021).
The tone is emotional.